{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081832794","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081832794"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 0ade777f-28a0-4101-945f-51e43f32f88f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081833844","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081833843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 0ade777f-28a0-4101-945f-51e43f32f88f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BA"," userResponse":" BA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081840810","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081840810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 0ade777f-28a0-4101-945f-51e43f32f88f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081841870","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081841870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 0ade777f-28a0-4101-945f-51e43f32f88f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081845100","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081845100"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 0ade777f-28a0-4101-945f-51e43f32f88f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081846142","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081846142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 0ade777f-28a0-4101-945f-51e43f32f88f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BO"," userResponse":" BO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081850264","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081850264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 0ade777f-28a0-4101-945f-51e43f32f88f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081851313","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081851313"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 0ade777f-28a0-4101-945f-51e43f32f88f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BU"," userResponse":" BU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081854786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081854786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 0ade777f-28a0-4101-945f-51e43f32f88f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" bu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081854938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081854938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 0ade777f-28a0-4101-945f-51e43f32f88f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ba..bu.asc.lc.16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BU"," userResponse":" BU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081865308","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081865307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081865542","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081865541"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081866523","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081866522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081867814","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081867813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081870746","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081870745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081871600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081871600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081871927","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081871927"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081873176","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081873176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081876743","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081876742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081877737","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081877736"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081878001","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081878000"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081878956","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081878955"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081881863","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081881863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081882910","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081882909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081883392","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081883391"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081887886","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081887884"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081888020","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081888020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 2d9ef1b9-ebba-4d2b-85de-c019151506e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081932479","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081932479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549081994150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549081994150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082000984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082000984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082005592","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082005592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082018558","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082018558"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082024373","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082024373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082041450","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082041450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082050760","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082050760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082075830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082075830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082081946","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082081946"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082087690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082087689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082100289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082100289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ff4f386a-356c-4b46-8541-41441886370d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082127150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082127150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_mka-me-vi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082134854","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082134854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_do-me-mo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082140986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082140985"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_do-me-mo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082182868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082182868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_su-ngu-me"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082212584","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082212584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_mje-me-tu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082220082","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082220082"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-to-ji"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082226329","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082226329"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_thi-njo-me"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082237031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082237031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_vyi-wo-me"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082249303","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082249302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ga-me-ba"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082258206","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082258206"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-msa-de"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082265405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082265405"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-mgo-ng'a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082271161","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082271161"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" d2307c13-6645-49ce-b514-f845dd456e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.all.stat.show.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-mgo-ng'a"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082282172","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082282171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082282406","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082282406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082283379","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082283378"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082284673","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082284673"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082287651","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082287650"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082288508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082288508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082288828","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082288828"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082290086","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082290085"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082293629","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082293628"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082294624","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082294623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082294888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082294888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082295843","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082295843"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082298754","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082298754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082299788","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082299788"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082300261","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082300261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082304805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082304804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082304888","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082304888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" c58de5fd-4147-4626-8d97-c05b5c54c22b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082328879","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082328879"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mfu_ne_me"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082335528","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082335528"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nge_me_va"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082343050","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082343050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nge_me_va"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082349675","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082349675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_me_mpe_mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082357218","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082357218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_me_mpe_mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082367626","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082367626"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_me_mpe_mle"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082374251","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082374251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mvu_me_be"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082380859","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082380858"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ngo_me_shu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082387482","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082387482"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_shi_me_fi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082394088","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082394088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_su_va_me"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082400752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082400752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ti_me_mwu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082407372","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082407372"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_me_di_hi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082414045","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082414045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mre_me_hu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082423026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082423026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_mre_me_hu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082463928","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082463928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" f14f0ba1-19c1-42cf-8f8a-681b4ddd45eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.me..me.noShow..2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_mre_me_hu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082477798","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082477798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_fe-ge-me"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082484901","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082484901"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-je-be"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082494790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082494790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ve-re-me"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082500773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082500773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_be-me-ge"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082509188","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082509188"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_mre-kwe-me"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082530366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082530366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_bwe-de-me"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" bwe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082535659","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082535659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_bwe-de-me"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082548714","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082548714"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_nye-me-be"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" nye"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082554375","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082554375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_nye-me-be"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082565723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082565723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ye-bwe-me"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" bwe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082572084","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082572084"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_ye-bwe-me"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082581113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082581113"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_mche-me-vye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082588740","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082588740"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-be-ze"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082594490","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082594487"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e1ede9bf-293f-4cc7-8f68-aec465605e4b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_me..me.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_me_me-be-ze"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082604967","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082604967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" faceb161-31b4-4674-bf78-1af862a03b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082605199","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082605197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" faceb161-31b4-4674-bf78-1af862a03b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082606178","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082606177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" faceb161-31b4-4674-bf78-1af862a03b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082607099","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082607099"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" faceb161-31b4-4674-bf78-1af862a03b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082607185","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082607185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" faceb161-31b4-4674-bf78-1af862a03b13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082620833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082620832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082621066","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082621065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082622039","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082622038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082623323","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082623322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082626290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082626290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082627158","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082627158"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082627480","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082627479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082628726","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082628725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082632290","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082632290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082633284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082633283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082633547","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082633546"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082634510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082634509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082637416","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082637416"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082638467","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082638467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082638947","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082638947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082643512","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082643511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082643620","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082643620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 16e30ac2-d4ed-466e-b3e7-4b56450f3978"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082655716","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082655715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MA"," userResponse":" MA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082660038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082660037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MA"," userResponse":" MA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082661630","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082661629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" me"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ME"," userResponse":" ME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082664749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082664749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" me"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082666305","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082666305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MI"," userResponse":" MI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082669284","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082669283"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082670841","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082670841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MO"," userResponse":" MO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082673917","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082673917"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082675486","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082675486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" MU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082679007","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082679007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082681031","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082681031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082681179","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082681179"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082713460","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082713460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" dae6ac19-0c89-4094-8bf2-3b2575fe03a0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082726581","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082726581"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ce180785-3f8d-4e79-a795-50ad8db6a8ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082727614","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082727614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ce180785-3f8d-4e79-a795-50ad8db6a8ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MA"," userResponse":" MA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082730554","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082730554"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ce180785-3f8d-4e79-a795-50ad8db6a8ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" me"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ME"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082731594","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082731594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ce180785-3f8d-4e79-a795-50ad8db6a8ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" me"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ME"," userResponse":" ME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082735730","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082735730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ce180785-3f8d-4e79-a795-50ad8db6a8ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082736759","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082736759"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ce180785-3f8d-4e79-a795-50ad8db6a8ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MI"," userResponse":" MI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082739508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082739508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ce180785-3f8d-4e79-a795-50ad8db6a8ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" MU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082741308","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082741308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ce180785-3f8d-4e79-a795-50ad8db6a8ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" MU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082744609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082744609"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ce180785-3f8d-4e79-a795-50ad8db6a8ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082744675","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082744675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ce180785-3f8d-4e79-a795-50ad8db6a8ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MU"," userResponse":" MU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082752264","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082752264"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" ce180785-3f8d-4e79-a795-50ad8db6a8ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ma..mu.asc.lc.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082767969","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082767969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082775151","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082775151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082796518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082796517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082808690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082808690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082814799","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082814799"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082823602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082823602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082831463","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082831463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082840789","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082840789"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082849026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082849026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" no"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082858430","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082858430"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082870215","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082870215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082876296","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082876296"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082882068","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082882066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" 372efa82-73bc-41bc-bbb4-8e48dbc93db6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082896576","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082896576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e03f3853-724e-461b-8244-9bc6c8314ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549082902398","data":{"timestamp":" 1549082902398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190202_073009"," gameId":" e03f3853-724e-461b-8244-9bc6c8314ace"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_7_3-4-7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}